<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:55:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HtB Cascade</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cascade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:55:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cascade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Cascade.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB-Cascade&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cascade is a medium difficulty Windows machine configured as a Domain Controller. LDAP anonymous binds are enabled, and enumeration yields the password for user &lt;code&gt;r.thompson&lt;/code&gt;, which gives access to a &lt;code&gt;TightVNC&lt;/code&gt; registry backup. The backup is decrypted to gain the password for &lt;code&gt;s.smith&lt;/code&gt;. This user has access to a .NET executable, which after decompilation and source code analysis reveals the password for the &lt;code&gt;ArkSvc&lt;/code&gt; account. This account belongs to the &lt;code&gt;AD Recycle Bin&lt;/code&gt; group, and is able to view deleted Active Directory objects. One of the deleted user accounts is found to contain a hardcoded password, which can be reused to login as the primary domain administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Escape</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 11:21:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-escape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Escape.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB-Escape&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Escape is a Medium difficulty Windows Active Directory machine that starts with an SMB share that guest authenticated users can download a sensitive PDF file. Inside the PDF file temporary credentials are available for accessing an MSSQL service running on the machine. An attacker is able to force the MSSQL service to authenticate to his machine and capture the hash. It turns out that the service is running under a user account and the hash is crackable. Having a valid set of credentials an attacker is able to get command execution on the machine using WinRM. Enumerating the machine, a log file reveals the credentials for the user &lt;code&gt;ryan.cooper&lt;/code&gt;. Further enumeration of the machine, reveals that a Certificate Authority is present and one certificate template is vulnerable to the ESC1 attack, meaning that users who are legible to use this template can request certificates for any other user on the domain including Domain Administrators. Thus, by exploiting the ESC1 vulnerability, an attacker is able to obtain a valid certificate for the Administrator account and then use it to get the hash of the administrator user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Giddy</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-giddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 10:46:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-giddy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Giddy.png&#34; alt=&#34;Giddy&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Giddy is a medium difficulty machine, which highlights how low privileged SQL Server logins can be used to compromise the underlying SQL Server service account. This is an issue in many environments, and depending on the configuration, the service account may have elevated privileges across the domain. It also features Windows registry enumeration and custom payload creation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Faculty</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:32:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-faculty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Faculty.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB Faculty&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faculty is a medium Linux machine that features a PHP web application that uses a library which is vulnerable to local file inclusion. Exploiting the LFi in this library reveals a password which can be used to log in as a low-level user called &lt;code&gt;gbyolo&lt;/code&gt; over SSH. The user &lt;code&gt;gbyolo&lt;/code&gt; has permission to run an &lt;code&gt;npm&lt;/code&gt; package called &lt;code&gt;meta-git&lt;/code&gt; as the &lt;code&gt;developer&lt;/code&gt; user. The version of the &lt;code&gt;meta-git&lt;/code&gt; installed on this box is vulnerable to code injection, which can be exploited to escalate the privileges to the user &lt;code&gt;developer&lt;/code&gt;. The privilege escalation to &lt;code&gt;root&lt;/code&gt; can be performed by exploiting the &lt;code&gt;CAP_SYS_PTRACE&lt;/code&gt; capability to inject shellcode into a process running as &lt;code&gt;root&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Jab</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-jab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:43:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-jab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Jab.png&#34; alt=&#34;Jab&#34;&gt;&#xA;Jab is a medium-difficulty Windows machine that features an Openfire XMPP server, hosted on a Domain Controller (DC). Public registration on the XMPP server allows the user to register an account. Then, by retrieving a list of all the users on the domain, a kerberoastable account is found, which allows the attacker to crack the retrieved hash for the user&amp;rsquo;s password. By visiting the account&amp;rsquo;s XMPP chat rooms, another account&amp;rsquo;s password is retrieved. This new account has DCOM privileges over the DC, thus granting the attacker local access on the machine. Finally, a malicious plugin uploaded through the locally-hosted Openfire Administration Panel gives the user SYSTEM access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Hospital</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:52:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-hospital/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Hospital.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB Hospital&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hospital is a medium-difficulty Windows machine that hosts an Active Directory environment, a web server, and a &lt;code&gt;RoundCube&lt;/code&gt; instance. The web application has a file upload vulnerability that allows the execution of arbitrary PHP code, leading to a reverse shell on the Linux virtual machine hosting the service. Enumerating the system reveals an outdated Linux kernel that can be exploited to gain root privileges, via &lt;a href=&#34;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-35001&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CVE-2023-35001&lt;/a&gt;. Privileged access allows &lt;code&gt;/etc/shadow&lt;/code&gt; hashes to be read and subsequently cracked, yielding credentials for the &lt;code&gt;RoundCube&lt;/code&gt; instance. Emails on the service hint towards the use of &lt;code&gt;GhostScript&lt;/code&gt;, which opens up the target to exploitation via &lt;a href=&#34;https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2023-36664&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CVE-2023-36664&lt;/a&gt;, a vulnerability exploited by crafting a malicious Embedded PostScript (EPS) file to achieve remote code execution on the Windows host. System access is then obtained by either of two ways: using a keylogger to capture &lt;code&gt;administrator&lt;/code&gt; credentials, or by abusing misconfigured &lt;code&gt;XAMPP&lt;/code&gt; permissions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Active</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-active/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:41:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-active/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Active.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB Active&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Active is an easy to medium difficulty machine, which features two very prevalent techniques to gain privileges within an Active Directory environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Cozyhosting</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cozyhosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:42:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cozyhosting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/htb-CozyHosting.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB CozyHosting&#34;&gt;&#xA;CozyHosting is an easy-difficulty Linux machine that features a &lt;code&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/code&gt; application. The application has the &lt;code&gt;Actuator&lt;/code&gt; endpoint enabled. Enumerating the endpoint leads to the discovery of a user&amp;rsquo;s session cookie, leading to authenticated access to the main dashboard. The application is vulnerable to command injection, which is leveraged to gain a reverse shell on the remote machine. Enumerating the application&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;.jar&lt;/code&gt; file, hardcoded credentials are discovered and used to log into the local database. The database contains a hashed password, which once cracked is used to log into the machine as the user &lt;code&gt;josh&lt;/code&gt;. The user is allowed to run &lt;code&gt;ssh&lt;/code&gt; as &lt;code&gt;root&lt;/code&gt;, which is leveraged to fully escalate privileges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of WiFi</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/dark-side-of-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:16:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/dark-side-of-wifi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/wifi-danger.png&#34; alt=&#34;Wifi Dangers&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your phone could be revealing your home WiFi information—and your location—to hackers without you even realizing it!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, convenience often comes at the cost of security and privacy. One overlooked yet serious risk is leaving WiFi enabled on personal devices when they are not in use. While having WiFi turned on might seem harmless, it can expose you to numerous cyber threats and privacy invasions. Below, we delve into the dangers of keeping WiFi enabled on your smartphone, laptop, or tablet and why it’s a habit you should reconsider.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Age of Ubiquitous Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/the-age-of-uts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 16:29:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/the-age-of-uts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/uts-main.png&#34; alt=&#34;Data Privacy Reaper&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world where technology seamlessly integrates into every aspect of our lives. Smartphones, wearables, smart home devices, vehicles, and even our daily internet activities constantly collect data about us. This era of ubiquitous technical surveillance has normalized the idea that our personal information is a commodity. But why should the average person care about data privacy?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RFID Badge Capture</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/the-rfid-badge-capture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 09:08:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/posts/the-rfid-badge-capture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/rfid-badge.png&#34; alt=&#34;RFID badge being scanned&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a penetration tester, the thrill of outwitting security systems is met with numerous challenges, especially when tasked with capturing and cloning an RFID badge. From maintaining stealth to overcoming technological limitations, the path is fraught with obstacles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/htb---cascade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/htb---cascade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;![[Cascade.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cascade is a medium difficulty Windows machine configured as a Domain Controller. LDAP anonymous binds are enabled, and enumeration yields the password for user &lt;code&gt;r.thompson&lt;/code&gt;, which gives access to a &lt;code&gt;TightVNC&lt;/code&gt; registry backup. The backup is decrypted to gain the password for &lt;code&gt;s.smith&lt;/code&gt;. This user has access to a .NET executable, which after decompilation and source code analysis reveals the password for the &lt;code&gt;ArkSvc&lt;/code&gt; account. This account belongs to the &lt;code&gt;AD Recycle Bin&lt;/code&gt; group, and is able to view deleted Active Directory objects. One of the deleted user accounts is found to contain a hardcoded password, which can be reused to login as the primary domain administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With over two decades of experience at the intersection of leadership, risk management, and cybersecurity, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the privilege of navigating the high-stakes world of national security. My journey as a counterintelligence special agent has been nothing short of exhilarating, filled with complex national security investigations, cutting-edge technical threat research, and the relentless pursuit of safeguarding our nation&amp;rsquo;s most sensitive assets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my various roles, I&amp;rsquo;ve orchestrated comprehensive threat and cyber intelligence operations, and led red team engagements that mimic real-world attack scenarios to expose vulnerabilities and bolster security. My expertise in detecting and neutralizing insider threats has proven crucial in maintaining the sanctity of critical infrastructures and organizational assets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
