<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Active Directory on </title>
    <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/tags/active-directory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Active Directory on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:55:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/tags/active-directory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HtB Cascade</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cascade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:55:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-cascade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Cascade.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB-Cascade&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cascade is a medium difficulty Windows machine configured as a Domain Controller. LDAP anonymous binds are enabled, and enumeration yields the password for user &lt;code&gt;r.thompson&lt;/code&gt;, which gives access to a &lt;code&gt;TightVNC&lt;/code&gt; registry backup. The backup is decrypted to gain the password for &lt;code&gt;s.smith&lt;/code&gt;. This user has access to a .NET executable, which after decompilation and source code analysis reveals the password for the &lt;code&gt;ArkSvc&lt;/code&gt; account. This account belongs to the &lt;code&gt;AD Recycle Bin&lt;/code&gt; group, and is able to view deleted Active Directory objects. One of the deleted user accounts is found to contain a hardcoded password, which can be reused to login as the primary domain administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Escape</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 11:21:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-escape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Escape.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB-Escape&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Escape is a Medium difficulty Windows Active Directory machine that starts with an SMB share that guest authenticated users can download a sensitive PDF file. Inside the PDF file temporary credentials are available for accessing an MSSQL service running on the machine. An attacker is able to force the MSSQL service to authenticate to his machine and capture the hash. It turns out that the service is running under a user account and the hash is crackable. Having a valid set of credentials an attacker is able to get command execution on the machine using WinRM. Enumerating the machine, a log file reveals the credentials for the user &lt;code&gt;ryan.cooper&lt;/code&gt;. Further enumeration of the machine, reveals that a Certificate Authority is present and one certificate template is vulnerable to the ESC1 attack, meaning that users who are legible to use this template can request certificates for any other user on the domain including Domain Administrators. Thus, by exploiting the ESC1 vulnerability, an attacker is able to obtain a valid certificate for the Administrator account and then use it to get the hash of the administrator user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Jab</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-jab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:43:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-jab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Jab.png&#34; alt=&#34;Jab&#34;&gt;&#xA;Jab is a medium-difficulty Windows machine that features an Openfire XMPP server, hosted on a Domain Controller (DC). Public registration on the XMPP server allows the user to register an account. Then, by retrieving a list of all the users on the domain, a kerberoastable account is found, which allows the attacker to crack the retrieved hash for the user&amp;rsquo;s password. By visiting the account&amp;rsquo;s XMPP chat rooms, another account&amp;rsquo;s password is retrieved. This new account has DCOM privileges over the DC, thus granting the attacker local access on the machine. Finally, a malicious plugin uploaded through the locally-hosted Openfire Administration Panel gives the user SYSTEM access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HtB Active</title>
      <link>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-active/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:41:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/writeups/htb-active/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://pL4sTiC1337.github.io/images/Active.png&#34; alt=&#34;HtB Active&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Active is an easy to medium difficulty machine, which features two very prevalent techniques to gain privileges within an Active Directory environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
